oldchicago.com 2016-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**Complete Terms & Conditions on our Personal Information Policy**

Privacy Policy Updates

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, we may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, we will post our updated Privacy Policy on our Site along with a change notice on the Site. We may also send registered users of our services a notice that this Privacy Policy has been changed. Your continued use of this Site and/or services and/or your continued provision of personally identifiable information to us after the posting of such notice will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

 **Information We Collect**

We may collect personal information (which is information that identifies you or relates to you as an identifiable person) about you such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, profile picture, social media account ID, and your communication preferences.

We may collect information from you when you interact with us such as when you register for an account, send us questions or requests, use our website, participate in a contest or sweepstakes promotion, or participate in our loyalty program.

 **Other Information We Collect About You:**

In addition, when you visit our Website, open our emails, use our apps, access the WiFi in any of our restaurants, or interact with our related tools, widgets or plug-ins, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies, web beacons and web server logs. The information we collect in this manner includes your IP address, unique device identifier, browser characteristics, domain and other system settings, search queries, device characteristics, operating system type, language preferences, referring URLs, actions taken on our site, dates and times of website visits, metadata and other information associated with other files stored on your device. 

A “cookie” is a file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A “web beacon,” also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies, and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. Through these automated collection methods, we obtain “clickstream data,” which is a log of the links and other content on which a visitor clicks while browsing a website. As the visitor clicks through the website, a record of the action may be collected and stored. We may link certain data elements we have collected through automated means, such as your browser information, with other information we have obtained about you to let us know, for example, whether you have opened an email we sent to you. Most Internet browsers allow you to remove or manage cookie functions and adjust your privacy and security preferences. For information on how to do this, access the “help” menu on your Internet browser. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of our Website.

We also may collect information about the location of the mobile device or tablet used to access the Website (“Location Data”). Location Data includes: (a) the location of the mobile device or tablet derived from GPS or WiFi use; (b) the IP address of the mobile device or tablet or internet service used to access the Website; and (c) other information made available by a user or others that indicates the current or prior location of the user, such as geotag information in photographs.

We will inform you if a specific Website, app or service collects precise Location Data. If you do not want us to collect Location Data from your device, please delete the app or disable the location settings on your device or tablet. Note, however, that disabling the location setting may affect your ability to access and use that app.

When you connect with social media though the Website, you may link with social media platforms and social media plug-ins (e.g., the Facebook "Like" button, "Share to Twitter" button) (collectively, “Social Media”). When accessing services through a Facebook or other social media account, we may (depending on the applicable user privacy settings) automatically have access to information provided to or through the social media platform. We may collect and use this information for the purposes described in this Policy or at the time the information was collected.

Information collected directly by the third party providers of the features is subject to the privacy policies or notices of these providers. We are not responsible for these providers’ information and privacy practices.

 **How We Use Your Information**

The information we collect from you helps us to identify ways that we can continue to serve you in the best way possible. _**We may use personal information for the following purposes**_ **:**

We may also aggregate and/or anonymize personal information for research, to improve our products and services; and for other business purposes.

 **Security**

We safeguard your information by taking reasonable steps to protect the information you provide us from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to help safeguard and secure your information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. No security system is 100% secure, thus we cannot ensure the security of information that you provide to us electronically and via our website.

 **Other Information You Should Know**
